Marriage. Betrayal. Murder.
Double Life is a mystery, thriller, drama film directed by Martin Wood.
A widow finds out from her late husband's mistress
that his death was not an accident.
Both women work together to unmask the truth behind the man they both loved.
Jo Creuzot, played by Javicia Leslie.
Sharon Setter, played by Pascale Hutton.
Larry, played by Vincent Gale.
Mark Setter, played by Niall Matter.
Sheldon Roberts, played by Aaron Douglas.
Louis Strand, played by John Cassini.
Body Double is a 1984 American neo-noir erotic thriller film
directed, co-written, and produced by Brian De Palma.
It stars Craig Wasson, Gregg Henry, Melanie Griffith, and Deborah Shelton.
The film is a direct homage to the 1950s films of Alfred Hitchcock, specifically Rear Window, Vertigo, and Dial M for
Murder, taking plot lines and themes (such as voyeurism, panic attack and obsession) from the first two.
At the time of its release, the film was a commercial failure, earning $8.8 million at the box office against a production budget of $10 million, as well as mixed
reviews, though Griffith's performance earned praise and earned her a nomination for the Golden Globe Award for Best Supporting Actress – Motion Picture.
Subsequently, the film received positive appraisal from cinema
fans and is now considered to be a cult film.
The tone is intense and emotional and mind_bending.